<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Spooked</title><link>https://feeds.simplecast.com/TBotaapn</link><description>Spooked features true-life supernatural stories, told firsthand by people who can barely believe it happened themselves. Be afraid. Created in the dark of night, by Snap Judgment Studios, in partnership with KQED &amp; PRX. It is hosted by Glynn Washington.Episodes drop every week on Friday! Spooked is available for free on ALL podcast platforms. Featuring brand NEW stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription.For Luminary subscribers, previously released episodes are still on Luminary.</description><item><title>Dearly Departed</title><link>podcasts/Dearly Departed.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Dearly departed, we are gathered here today to get through this thing called Spooked. Most of the ghosties and ghoulies we meet on this show have sinister agendas. But sometimes, spirits reach through the veil to send tender messages: I’m here; I miss you; remember me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doris&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doris While out on a drive with her best friends in Victoria, British Columbia, Lyn encounters one of the city’s most famous ghosts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Lyn, for introducing us to Doris!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Andrew Butler, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mama Bear&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mama Bear Desiree’s grandmother died just before she was born. But Desiree has certainly met her grandmother, long after her death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Desiree, for sharing your story with the Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Nicholas Marks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/8a29af75-04b2-4f4a-b2ce-2a1ff48618d8/3000x3000/dearlydeparted-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The White Hand</title><link>podcasts/The White Hand.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Katia thinks that the dated wallpaper is the worst thing the last tenant’s left behind in her family’s new home. She’s in for a big surprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Katia, for sharing your story with the Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Yari Bundy, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch and listen to Spooked... you can subscribe on &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; for our scary stories.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/2da87b2c-b705-4f67-beae-e57368fcaca9/3000x3000/whitehand-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Cedar Hills</title><link>podcasts/Cedar Hills.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;15-year-old Couita and her family move into a rental house in Cedar Hills, Texas. As soon as her Dad leaves on a work trip, a stranger moves in to keep them company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to, Couita Nucosse, for sharing your story with Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch and listen to Spooked... you can subscribe on &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; for our scary stories.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/b9d4a4a5-035e-48e4-b83a-c8fe997248a0/3000x3000/cedarhills-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Blue Lady</title><link>podcasts/The Blue Lady.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Castles are the stuff of fairy tales, of happily-ever-afters, right? Well, things are not so rosy at Sharon Rectory in misty Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Emma, for sharing your story with us! If you want to hear more about her family’s haunted castle, check out Emma’s book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/HAUNTING-SHARON-RECTORY-Horror-Heartbreak-ebook/dp/B084MHGQVH" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Haunting of Sharon Rectory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;﻿&lt;/strong&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch and listen to Spooked... you can &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;subscribe on YouTube&lt;/a&gt; for our scary stories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 8 Nov 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/42b409d4-c986-4de6-9e84-f6e1f461898a/3000x3000/thebluelady-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>This Olde House</title><link>podcasts/This Olde House.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Rich is renovating an old house in the town of Wells, in Somerset, England. It has history dating back to the 15th century… and not all of it has stayed in the past. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Rich, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Yari Bundy, scouted by Sasha Wilson, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Happy Halloween!!! Thank you for rocking this Spooky Season with us... you are the best Spooksters in the world! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch and listen to Spooked... you can &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;subscribe on YouTube&lt;/a&gt; for our scary stories.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 23:17:25 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/312eea62-da04-4dc6-bd0d-9a420341d57d/3000x3000/thisoldehouse-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Uncle Charlie</title><link>podcasts/Uncle Charlie.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Todd receives a box with photographs from his grandmother who had recently passed away.  Skimming through the photos, Todd finds a picture of a man in WWII army attire. Immediately, he has flashbacks of childhood memories he long forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Todd, for sharing your story with the Spooked! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yáñez, original score by Lalin St. Juste, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Happy Halloween Season Spooksters! Now you can also &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;subscribe on YouTube&lt;/a&gt; for scary stories from Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/6d6f8f83-5d25-496f-a661-39a3b66c63f4/3000x3000/unclecharlie-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Night of the Living Bed</title><link>podcasts/Night of the Living Bed.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Reena lives in Jammu, India. She prays every night before going to sleep. But one night her bed has other plans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Reena, for sharing your story to Spooked! We are so very glad that you can sleep through the night now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yáñez, original scored by Doug Stuart, scouted by Aditya Mattoo, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spooked has a Youtube Channel! &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for a new scary story each week. Happy October Spooky PPL! 'Tis the Season to celebrate the Shadow!!! &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/69c3e3d1-abae-4394-98d6-f8d01b104308/3000x3000/livingbed-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Mother of Bunafu</title><link>podcasts/Mother of Bunafu.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;David travels to the small village of Bunafu in Uganda to visit his family. One morning, he’s awakened by people celebrating a marriage. To his surprise, his mother is the new bride. And the groom? None other than the village spirit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, David, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yáñez, original score by Sandra Lawson-Ndu, scouted by Lulu Jemimah, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spooked has a Youtube Channel! &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/@spookedpodcast"&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; for a new scary story each week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/cd10a843-abc0-4802-b60c-1955a2c89ace/3000x3000/motherofbunafu-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Spooked LIVE: Glynn Washington x John Blake</title><link>podcasts/Spooked LIVE: Glynn Washington x John Blake.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Glynn's brother pays him a visit. And Journalist, John Blake, shares his family story about a ghost that sought forgiveness from beyond the grave. These stories were told at Spooked LIVE at the haunted Orpheum Theatre in Los Angeles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks, John, for sharing your story with us! To learn more about John's story reconciling with his mother’s family, be sure to check out his amazing memoir — &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/More-Than-Imagined-Discovered-Mother/dp/0593443047"&gt;More Than I Imagined: What  A Black Man Discovered About the White Mother He Never Knew&lt;/a&gt;. You can also follow his work on his &lt;a href="https://johnkblake.com/"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story was produced by Zoë Ferrigno and Davey Kim. The original score was created and performed live by Doug Stuart and Brijean Murphy. Artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spooked has a Youtube Channel! &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/@spookedpodcast  "&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; for a new scary story each week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 4 Oct 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/00af1069-3417-4a1d-8f15-5df82aa26f20/3000x3000/spookedlive-sq-1.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Piper from the Past</title><link>podcasts/Piper from the Past.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When bagpiper Steve moved to York, England, he joined a local pipe band. Little did he know that he’d have a piper from the past join him from the other side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Steve, for sharing your story with Spooked! If you’re ever in York, you can hear Steve’s Piper Tale in the flesh by joining &lt;a href="https://www.theoriginalghostwalkofyork.co.uk/"&gt;The Original Ghost Walk of York&lt;/a&gt;. Want more tunes? Check out performances from Steve’s band: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/NYfireband"&gt;North Yorkshire Fire &amp; Rescue Service Pipe Band&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by George McDonagh, original score by Clay Xavier, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spooked has a Youtube Channel! &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/@spookedpodcast  "&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; for a new scary story each week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/e89a6248-0a00-4419-8ea4-ba043ff44dfd/3000x3000/piperfromthepast-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Haunted Haunted House</title><link>podcasts/The Haunted Haunted House.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aspiring filmmaker Chase finds the perfect place to shoot his horror film... the Arx Mortis Haunted House. But beware: inside this Halloween attraction, not all of the scares are fake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Chase Barnett, for sharing your story with Spooked! Check out Chase’s podcast &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5gX6TfuetFxkeCiIKgBMkb?si=e0df911654504ebf"&gt;Holed Up&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yáñez, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spooked has a Youtube Channel! &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/@spookedpodcast  "&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; for a new scary story each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Happy Spooky Season Spooky PPL!&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/f970b882-09bb-4961-823c-576b2f4e1276/3000x3000/hauntedhauntedhouse-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Northern Frights</title><link>podcasts/Northern Frights.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;As an engineer, Forrest is used to being able to solve problems and find solutions. But while working in the remote North Slope of Alaska, he learns that there are things in this world that just can’t be explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A big thanks to Forrest for sharing his story with the Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Doug Stuart, artwork by Teo Ducot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAPPY FRIDAY THE 13th SPOOKSTERS!!! Today kicks off a ritual as old as our treachery: Season of the Wolf. Brand new episodes will drop each and every week until All Hallows' Eve. Cross over and listen on podcast platforms everywhere. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/56ec475b-055f-41cf-bdd4-6bf57cf25dea/3000x3000/northernfrights-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Paint It Black</title><link>podcasts/Paint It Black.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When you put brush to canvas you expect to create something that exists outside of yourself. But what if that something is completely evil?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paint it Black &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most down-to-earth family you will ever meet brushes up with evil forces. Brian, Christian, Mary, and Bridget Mahovlic share what happened to them when they came face-to-face with something demonic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you to Brian, Christian, Mary, and Bridget Mahovlic for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Eliza Smith, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Red Canvas &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jackie and her friends were partying when they made the painting. It was a group effort: they each painted a different part of the canvas. But when they finished, and saw what they had made, they knew they had created something evil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jackie Hill, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Renzo Gorrio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 6 Sep 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/dd1404ed-b9e9-48a0-966c-a7471ab02c86/3000x3000/paintitblack-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Deliver Me From Evil</title><link>podcasts/Deliver Me From Evil.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Marianne is a typical teenager. She’s having growing pains, throwing temper tantrums, and feeling different from all her peers. Except Marianne might actually be very different from everyone around her because she might actually be possessed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Marianne, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Ella June Pierson, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/5732a09e-e807-42f5-8bd3-412221275632/3000x3000/deliverme-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Season IX Trailer</title><link>podcasts/Season IX Trailer.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting Friday the 13th of September, Spooked marks a ritual older than time... &lt;i&gt;Season of the Wolf. &lt;/i&gt;Brand new episodes will drop each and every week until All Hallows' Eve! Eight separate journeys into the void. Be afraid. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spooked Season 9... cross over and listen on podcast platforms everywhere 9/13/24.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/d5a0d310-d35c-447a-8711-1665c98e92cd/a531c897-cd58-4a9c-ac8e-e0a77fae3926/3000x3000/spooked-season9-kqed-1400x1400.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Playtime</title><link>podcasts/Playtime.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Caro saw a gift box in her kitchen, she knew she was in for a surprise. But some gifts come with a price. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Caro, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yáñez, original score by Dirk Schwarzhoff, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f10662d6-1ba8-4d11-acad-e6ceb8c90992/3000x3000/playtime-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Well</title><link>podcasts/The Well.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On one side of the basement little Rowan has his toys, but on the other side, in the corner, there is a deep dark hole oozing water and something… trying to get out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Rowan, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Doug Stuart, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/011dff1f-8961-4ff7-be8d-a3ddb000cff8/3000x3000/hauntedwell-viii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Tall Man in The Hat</title><link>podcasts/Tall Man in The Hat.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Amy is a nurse’s assistant in a progressive care unit. One day, one of Amy’s patients says to her: “The tall man in the hat doesn’t like you.” Later that day, the woman passes away. Then, a few months later, the &lt;em&gt;exact same thing &lt;/em&gt;happens. And then it happens again… and again… and again…&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Amy, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoe Ferrigno, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 9 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/ccbab84d-b60e-48cb-b2a5-d1b3e9b20219/3000x3000/img-1047.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Bull Boy</title><link>podcasts/Bull Boy.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;While Dan is at the compound of good friends and prominent members of the Blackfeet Traditional Medicine community, the Heavyrunner family, he learns just how important it is to practice good medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Dan SaSuweh Jones for sharing your story with us! &lt;a href="https://sasuweh.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; about Dan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 2 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c794871f-f4fa-4cb5-bad8-34fde34e94f7/3000x3000/bullboyviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Panic Room</title><link>podcasts/Panic Room.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah thinks she’s found the perfect new apartment in San Francisco. But she’s in for a surprise…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Sarah, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d8e33f73-0300-4be4-969f-c7e51cdec24f/3000x3000/panicroom2-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>George</title><link>podcasts/George.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Just because you make friends with the ghost in your apartment building, doesn’t mean all your neighbors will follow suit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, April and Joan, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Richard Haig, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a77a7dce-06a7-400f-85ee-20f9b862b453/3000x3000/georgeviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Knock Knock</title><link>podcasts/Knock Knock.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In a boarding house in Chicago, a young girl puts her questions to the universe and the answers are returned in coded messages from the other side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BIG thanks to Connie Shirakawa for sharing her story with us. Connie is a storyteller in Chicago. You can catch some of her performances on her website. &lt;a href="https://www.connieshirakawa.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.connieshirakawa.com/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Doug Stuart, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/2dd44e7f-d29a-40d8-a709-95e5672137ef/3000x3000/knockknock-viii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>A Mother Knows</title><link>podcasts/A Mother Knows.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;We all know it’s good to be a little scared of your parents. But TK has a whole other list of reasons to be terrified of his mom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you kindly, TK, for sharing your story with us. We also want to thank Laura at the &lt;a href="https://www.paranormalscholar.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paranormal Scholar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for helping us find this amazing story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford and Eliza Smith. Original score by Richard Haig. Artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 5 Jul 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/7e9cc5b8-9725-4c78-bb3c-b2b9e2dc9e92/3000x3000/amotherknows-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Old Hady</title><link>podcasts/Old Hady.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jack and his family move to an old farmhouse in the middle of the country, looking for a place to call their own. But they may not be the new owners after all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jack Irons, for sharing your story with Spooked! And thank you, Hady... for taking care of Jack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yañez, scouted by Elizabeth Pardue, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/fda58ba9-1928-4589-ba9e-5dc4589fae48/3000x3000/oldhady-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Sister Sister</title><link>podcasts/Sister Sister.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Identical twin sisters Melissa and Michelle Macedo are inseparable. They’re each other’s “own little world.” But the new girl… wants to change all that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big thanks to Melissa and Michelle Macedo for sharing your story with the Spooked! Melissa and Michelle aren’t just Spooksters. They have their own band, called Macedo… check it out!! &lt;a href="http://www.macedomusic.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.macedomusic.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e71b0b98-edaa-437f-a114-3fdd3e3717b3/3000x3000/sistersisterviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Jorge's Gift</title><link>podcasts/Jorge's Gift.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jorge's grandfather was a wise, gifted man with the ability to see things others can only feel. When he passed away, he left Jorge with a legacy that he was not ready to handle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jorge &amp; Alejandra, for sharing your story with Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Yari Bundy, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/4e288289-caee-46a6-9ba6-ba8997a47ec7/3000x3000/jorgesgiftviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>I Know What You Did Next Summer</title><link>podcasts/I Know What You Did Next Summer.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Should you heed your dreams if they foretell danger? How can you tell the difference between dreams and what might become reality?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Denver Deja Vu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jodi is about to discover that the man of her dreams is a walking, talking nightmare. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jodi, for sharing your story with us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Lauryn Newson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lady and the Scamp&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When someone in a hockey mask starts following Silvana in her dreams, she realizes that sometimes you don’t want all your dreams to come true. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Silvana, for sharing your story with us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, Nathalie Chicha, original score by Renzo Gorrio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jun 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e7e3a258-af81-4830-8b20-3f11e6d78f7b/3000x3000/iknowwhatyoudidnextsummer-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Monster Spray</title><link>podcasts/Monster Spray.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jennie and her family love their new house. If only the screaming would stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jennie + fam, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Nichk Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0f3da9c9-77ea-45a2-b538-0e4b68849403/3000x3000/monsterspray-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hidden in Plain Sight</title><link>podcasts/Hidden in Plain Sight.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes we don’t need to look under the bed, or inside of the closet. Sometimes, the monster isn’t hidden at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STORIES &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come Play with Me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Paulette’s daughter starts talking to an imaginary friend, she thinks it’s normal a childhood rite until the day she hears the friend talk back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Paulette, for sharing your story with Spooked! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Eliza Smith, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Hotel Beaumont&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Beilfuss works in mortuaries and retirement homes, but he doesn’t believe in ghosts. But he starts to question everything when he moves into an old-age home and a hospice center called the Hotel Beaumont. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Dave Beilfuss and Holly Evans for sharing your story with us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Liz Mak, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/cce01646-eef5-4be1-a8dd-12b6cc687e95/3000x3000/hiddeninplainsight-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>I Think We're Alone Now</title><link>podcasts/I Think We're Alone Now.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Usually ghosts linger to deliver a message, to let us know what happened to them, why they need to stay behind. But what if the ghost stays behind to let us know something about ourselves? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Naynay, for sharing your story with the Spooked! If you know somebody who doesn’t feel like they fit in, maybe you feel that way yourself, be sure to check out the &lt;a href="https://itgetsbetter.org/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;It Gets Better Project&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Richard Haig, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/4b0eb23c-4161-43da-a564-1373270918bc/3000x3000/ithinkwe-realonenow-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Planes, Trains, and Ghostmobiles</title><link>podcasts/Planes, Trains, and Ghostmobiles.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Who says that a ghost can’t help you get from point A to point B?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORIES &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ghost Ride the Whip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joey and his dad take a car ride that they will never, ever, &lt;em&gt;ever&lt;/em&gt; forget.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big love to Joey for sharing his story with the Spooked! If you want to hear more from Joey, check out his podcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/trailer-trashing/id1508247726"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trailer Trashing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Alyia Yates, original score by Shane Bingham&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bike Angel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the middle of the night in Ciudad Neza, Mexico. Nayma is coming home from a party, and she’s all alone. How will she get home safe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Nayma, for sharing your story with us! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Fernando Hernandez, original score by Renzo Gorrio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Translation by&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Fernando Hernandez and&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Adreanna Rodriguez&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/67f46ade-93d5-429b-92a4-806e6d30ac65/3000x3000/planestrainsghostmobiles-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Picture Perfect</title><link>podcasts/Picture Perfect.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A picture is worth a thousand words. Unless it leaves you speechless. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Picture Perfect&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Susiy and her family visit a new town, they have no idea who they’ll be running into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suisy, thank you for sharing your story with us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Lalin St. Juste&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Screenshot Ghost &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grise is working night shift in the nursing home. One night, something’s making mischief… and it’s not a patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Grise, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Nicolas Marx&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 3 May 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/bffe006a-83f8-4994-a977-aca1ae19e35f/3000x3000/pictureperfect-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Miller House</title><link>podcasts/The Miller House.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Some houses possess a presence. Some houses make strange noises. Some houses… come with a man in a green suit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the Strohm family for sharing your story!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Doug Stuart&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/3a0ba796-94fe-4169-9314-f376c7bdecf1/3000x3000/millerhousexiii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Ghostlighted</title><link>podcasts/Ghostlighted.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ellie’s mom doesn’t believe her when she says the house is haunted. But when a shadow man appears in Ellie’s closet doorway one night, Ellie wonders: who can she turn to?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Ellie, for sharing your story with us here at Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Richard Haig, artwork by Sanaa Khan&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0c64dc65-a728-47da-8960-9ec85cd70b6d/3000x3000/ghostlighted-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hellevator</title><link>podcasts/Hellevator.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Just because it looks like you’re all alone… doesn’t mean you are. If someone in the darkness calls out to you, don’t answer them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STORIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hellevator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dan is a cop on the nightshift. When he’s asked to check something out at the deserted senior home, he discovers one resident never left. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Dan Cope, for sharing your story with us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Richard Haig&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Queen Mary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Queen Mary is one of the most haunted places in America. But Daniel and his friends don’t take any heed of the history when they’re asked to spend the night aboard the ship. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Daniel Noah, for sharing another terrifying tale with us. Daniel makes horror films and he also makes podcasts about horror films. Check out his amazing podcast: &lt;a href="https://luminary.link/PncOb0i7s5"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visitations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by Eliza Smith, original score by Lauryn Newson&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8004e434-3b0f-4f5f-8917-488973d64ecc/3000x3000/hellavator-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Quince Años</title><link>podcasts/Quince Años.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Paola’s quinceañera will have sunflowers, dancing and a guest list that’s out of this world. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Paola González, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Produced by Erick Yañez, original score by Doug Stuart, translation by Lou Arruti, artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 5 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/dd5b5ef2-43a1-48c8-91e3-91907de174ff/3000x3000/quincean-os-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Tagalong Pt. 2</title><link>podcasts/The Tagalong Pt. 2.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;In our last episode of Spooked we met Aimee, she can see and talk to ghosts. She even invites one to come home with her and be her best friend. If you haven’t heard the last episode -- you’re going to want to go back and listen to that one first. Part two of a two-part story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Aimee, for sharing your story with Spooked! Aimee makes awesome handmade paper items, check out her &lt;a href="https://www.ebay.com/usr/aimecoulthurs0?_trksid=p2047675.l2559" target="_blank"&gt;store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Jordain Wallace, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/20db3e42-4aad-445d-97d2-b0c937a8d68a/3000x3000/tagalongpt2-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Tagalong Pt. 1</title><link>podcasts/The Tagalong Pt. 1.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Aimee is different from her classmates: she can see and talk to ghosts. She even invites one to come home with her and be her best friend. Part one of a two-part story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Aimee, for sharing your story with Spooked! Aimee makes awesome handmade paper items, check out her &lt;a href="https://www.ebay.com/usr/aimecoulthurs0?_trksid=p2047675.l2559" target="_blank"&gt;store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Jordain Wallace, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8d196a1e-b8e1-4027-a3ce-b7688f563ae7/3000x3000/tagalongpt1-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Old Church Road</title><link>podcasts/Old Church Road.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Chantal’s dad insists the house is fine. Chantal’s mom says the place is haunted and gives her the creeps. Chantal doesn’t want to pick sides, but she knows her mom is onto something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode contains mention of suicide and massacres, sensitive listeners please be advised.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Chantal, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Dakim, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/825533ea-4570-43d4-93f2-9e46aed01bea/3000x3000/oldchurchrd-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Closet Dolls</title><link>podcasts/Closet Dolls.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Octavia doesn’t let anyone near her dolls. Sure seems like the dolls want to get near to her, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Octavia, for sharing your story with us here at Spooked! Octavia Sexton is an Appalachian storyteller and teaching artist in Kentucky. Learn more about Octavia at her &lt;a href="https://octaviasexton.com/" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Doug Stuart, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 8 Mar 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/20653b0f-df3d-408d-820b-d966fbf789cc/3000x3000/closet-dolls-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>30-Day Notice</title><link>podcasts/30-Day Notice.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You know that house, the one at the end of the block? The one the kids all dare each other to break into? Well, Mary El is about to move into it. And she’s pretty sure the landlord isn’t telling her family something important about the house’s past. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Mary El Grammer, for sharing your story with us! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 1 Mar 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e036d434-3643-45bc-8707-a8ed305a4334/3000x3000/30daynotice-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Occupants</title><link>podcasts/The Occupants.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Old houses have seen so many occupants. And just because former tenants have moved out, doesn’t mean they’ve truly left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STORIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirror in the Bathroom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Pastor Sara Bishop looks in the mirror at her new house, she can’t see herself. She can see the last tenant... and he’s been dead for a long time. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Sara, for sharing your story with Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Haunted Hacienda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re not supposed to mess around with mirrors and Bloody Mary. You’re not supposed to mess around with Ouija boards. And you’re definitely not supposed to mess around with white magic. But Jose Moreno and his friends don’t know that... yet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jose Moreno, for sharing your story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick with help from Erick Yañez. Original score by Davey Kim. Artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/35eec70a-4d56-4984-9d79-fd78c7310f8c/3000x3000/occupants-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Man On The Mesa</title><link>podcasts/Man On The Mesa.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Jayson first arrives at Camp Pendleton, he knows that the military base has quite a history. But he’s about to find out just how active history can be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jayson, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/aa2aa475-77b7-4d28-950f-ba60a71baccf/3000x3000/manonthemesa-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Opal</title><link>podcasts/Opal.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jessica keeps seeing her least favorite great aunt, Opal. She keeps telling her grandma, make Opal leave me alone. But Jessica’s grandma can’t do anything… because Opal’s been dead for weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jessica, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Clay Xavier, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 9 Feb 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/1235b41b-4a0c-4c8f-b809-2c67395dddb3/3000x3000/opal-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Medicine People</title><link>podcasts/Medicine People.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Amelia’s trapped in a bad marriage. Her dad has a secret to get her out. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story contains themes of domestic abuse. Please take care while listening.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Amelia, for sharing your story with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Yari Bundy. Special thanks to Cody Harjo and Ezra Vazquez-D'Amico. Artwork by Teo Ducot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 2 Feb 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/1ac1add8-a437-45bb-833c-186ff1b48aa6/3000x3000/medicinepeople-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Red Balloon</title><link>podcasts/The Red Balloon.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sabina starts to get a creeping feeling that she’s not alone in her childhood home in Perth, Australia. She wonders what could be there. But when she finally finds out… she can’t believe her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Sabina, for sharing your story with Spooked! If you want more stories from Sabina, check out her book:&lt;a href="https://groveatlantic.com/book/muckross-abbey-and-other-stories/" target="_blank"&gt; Muckross Abbey and Other Stories&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Lalin St. Juste, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/2b9e9b87-d4c3-47f3-87e2-29390e46076b/3000x3000/carnivalballoon-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hands Without A Face</title><link>podcasts/Hands Without A Face.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone in Diane’s house has a different bedtime. When someone sits on the edge of her bed, waking her up, she’s not shocked. Until she looks to see who it is, and no one’s there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Diane, Brian, Xavier, Charlie, and Bennett for sharing your story with us here at Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Doug Stuart, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/cc8164e2-7cea-4f49-a475-55db567c432e/3000x3000/handswithoutafaceix-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Paperboy</title><link>podcasts/The Paperboy.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ray Christian hated being a paperboy. Bad pay, hard route, rude customers. But there was one customer in particular who was different from the rest, and Ray didn’t quite know why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Dr. Ray Christian, for sharing your story with us. Check out more of Ray's stories on his podcast, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://luminary.link/h97lFo0OM3" target="_blank"&gt;What’s Ray Saying?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Liz Mak, original score Leon Morimoto, art by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/28e6115c-5382-4b3e-ba27-4ce9747b6a32/3000x3000/paperboy-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hurricane Helpers</title><link>podcasts/Hurricane Helpers.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Brittnay and her family are trying to get out of the path of Hurricane Rita. But when they get stuck out on the road… all they can do is pray for a miracle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to Brittnay and her parents Steve and Cindy for sharing their story with Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Doug Stuart, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year, Spooksters! We are so grateful for all of you. Our spooky fam can’t wait to travel to the other side of the veil again with you this year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 5 Jan 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/cba4f4f8-c4ca-4039-8a6d-27abe3400572/3000x3000/hurricanehelpers-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Yellow Balloon</title><link>podcasts/The Yellow Balloon.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Richard moves into an old farmhouse next to a big cornfield, he’s pretty sure that it’s haunted. And the ghosts… well, they’re not exactly friendly. He wants to know: how does he protect himself from supernatural forces?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Richard Haynie, for sharing your story with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Leon Moriomoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/21fdd6ac-3742-49b7-8d6d-e890f28916a2/3000x3000/yellowballoon-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Murmur</title><link>podcasts/The Murmur.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah and her dad are hearing the same noise. It’s coming from somewhere upstairs, from somewhere in the wall. It sounds like someone’s talking, whispering, murmuring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Sarah and Richard Benkin for sharing your story. If you want more scary stories from Sarah, check out her horror anthologies, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Then-Was-Dark-Various/dp/0996140115" target="_blank"&gt;Then It Was Dark&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://birdcage-bottom-books.myshopify.com/products/built-on-strange-ground" target="_blank"&gt;Built on Strange Ground&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e46727ca-d3d2-46ca-8fb1-9269ff35f27b/3000x3000/themurmur-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Buffer Night</title><link>podcasts/Buffer Night.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;One wrong turn leads Kyan and his friends to the most sinister encounter of their lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story contains explicit language, sensitive listeners please be advised.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Kyan Bond for sharing his story! If you know what’s up with Buffer Night, drop us a line, and we’ll make sure Kyan gets it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Dirk Schwartzhoff, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 17:34:41 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/74c909c2-a803-48b1-8293-fe26376a1b7d/3000x3000/buffernight-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Creature Feature</title><link>podcasts/Creature Feature.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Strange creatures don't just live under your bed. Oh no. In this Spooked episode, we dive deep into the waters of an Oregon lake &amp; travel to the island of Montserrat to bring you tales of things that go bump in the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Devil’s Lake&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zack is visiting the Oregon Coast with family when he, his dad, and his uncle decide to head to nearby Devil’s Lake to do some fishing. When a creature with greenish blue skin jumps out of the water to grab him he begins to understand the true darkness of the lake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Zach, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Ligaroo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Shirley Spycalla was a little girl, her family lived on the Caribbean island of Grenada, where she was always told to get home before dark. One day, she finds out why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Shirley, for sharing your story with Spooked. Shirley now lives on the small and beautiful island of Montserrat, where she stays on eternal guard for shapeshifters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Doug Stuart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 8 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/03851cae-3f4f-409c-aac2-941fe0f69562/3000x3000/creaturefeature-viii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Rocking Horse</title><link>podcasts/The Rocking Horse.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Elizabeth was 19, she got a job as an au pair for an 11-year-old girl named Amy. The girl and her parents lived on a horse farm in rural Georgia - it was remote and beautiful. But at night, when the house got dark and quiet, someone moved through the halls, waiting, and watching for Elizabeth. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Elizabeth, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 1 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e1cceb7b-e47f-482a-99aa-f69574f8aefa/3000x3000/rockinghorse-vii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Las Tres Cruces</title><link>podcasts/Las Tres Cruces.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s the 1990s in Popoyán, Colombia. Twenty-year-old Humberto and his two best friends Jairo and Mauricio set off for an adventure in the woods. They think they’re invincible–but they’re no match for what they encounter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, thank you, Humberto for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Lalin St. Juste, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/5166c1ed-09be-4047-b00c-c1677402783d/3000x3000/lastrescruces-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>These Boots Are Made For Stalking</title><link>podcasts/These Boots Are Made For Stalking.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;What happens when everyone in the family can see the same specter… but they don’t tell each other for years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story contains explicit language - sensitive listeners please be advised.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Michelle, Sherri, and Ed for sharing your story with the Spooked. This story comes to us from the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/stories-with-sapphire/id1495941921" target="_blank"&gt;Stories with Sapphire podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, listen &amp; subscribe for some scary stuff!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e5929252-407d-44d8-bc4f-2c40191e2f79/3000x3000/thesebootsaremadefor-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Banker</title><link>podcasts/The Banker.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Antonio and his sister Anita were growing up in Texas, their family didn’t have much money. That’s why they were so excited to move into their very own home, even if it was a little run-down. It turns out, the home already had an occupant. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Antonio and Anita, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8c5348d9-d316-4d6c-a46c-a4e07dbc963d/3000x3000/bankerghost-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Pet Cemetery</title><link>podcasts/Pet Cemetery.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Ray was a kid, he took care of all the animals in his neighborhood… even after they were gone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Ray, for sharing your story with us! Ray’s podcast, &lt;a href="https://medium.com/prxofficial/prx-and-the-moth-to-present-new-episodes-of-the-whats-ray-saying-podcast-b2eefcdc9aae" target="_blank"&gt;What’s Ray Saying&lt;/a&gt;, returns next week! Enter a world of Southern-baked personal narratives and Black American history. New episodes drop November 8, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Lauryn Newson, produced by Chris Hambrick, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 3 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/9720b658-1798-40a8-bba6-dff94bb3c7ef/3000x3000/petcemetary-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Woods Have Eyes</title><link>podcasts/The Woods Have Eyes.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Nate and Keith love to explore the forests in Massachusetts and Rhode Island, hunting for stones and crystals to add to their collection. But something out there is also on the hunt… for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you Nate for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Doug Stuart, produced by Erick Yáñez, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HAPPY HALLOWEEN SPOOKSTERS!!! We appreciate each and every one of you so so much. Cheers to you  and yours this spooky season &lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:43:16 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a0a900ea-357d-49a0-bdf5-e4eebd6579a3/3000x3000/thehillshaveeyes-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Creature Feature II</title><link>podcasts/Creature Feature II.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When a creature shows itself, wonder fills you, terror compels you, but which will you follow? Two friends in the countryside, and two men at sea are put to the test by mysterious beings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silver Man&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Martin and Louise visit an abandoned house, something is waiting for them–but not on the grounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Martin, for sharing the mystery with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Clay Xavier, produced by Anne Ford&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Somethin’ Fishy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a fisherman, Clyde spends most of his time on the water. He’s seen all kinds of creatures out there… whales, squid, sharks. But when it comes to the ocean, there’s always a bigger fish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Clyde, for sharing your story with us. We hope you never see that thing again… But if you do, you know who to call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Seth Marceau, produced by Zoë Ferrigno&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/47e8463c-bbc3-4ba2-b3ca-2e698fd2fd8e/3000x3000/somethinfishy-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Lady Grim</title><link>podcasts/Lady Grim.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sherry and her husband keep seeing a hooded figure around their farm in Nova Scotia. She isn’t a ghost. She’s there to collect souls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Sherry, for sharing your story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/600094d6-f4c7-4dad-9936-af161b8524dd/3000x3000/ladygrim-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Lighthouse</title><link>podcasts/The Lighthouse.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Heceta Lighthouse Bed &amp; Breakfast on the Oregon Coast used to be a lightkeeper’s home–and it has a reputation for being very haunted. So Spooked producer, Zoë Ferrigno, went to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Doug Stuart, produced by Pam Porter’s Granddaughter, Zoë Ferrigno, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Friday the 13th, Spooksters!!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/dde75d33-a068-4726-8093-22348a33a046/3000x3000/lighthouse-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Domovoi</title><link>podcasts/The Domovoi.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sure, you’ve heard of a gnome, a troll, a sprite, an orc, a Babadook, a centaur, a tomten... but have you ever heard of a Domovoi? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Nikita, for sharing your story with us. We also want to thank Laura at the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paranormalscholar.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Paranormal Scholar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for helping us find this amazing story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Eliza Smith, original score by Leon Moriomoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 6 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/b196f915-39e7-4247-9c52-585df1bd04cc/3000x3000/domovoi-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Brick and Mortal</title><link>podcasts/Brick and Mortal.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the spirits we encounter are benevolent and kind — like guardian angels. And sometimes, they wait, and watch, and wish us ill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eunice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tiffany’s keeps waking up in the middle of the night to the sound of someone walking around her room. Finally, one night, a woman materializes right in front of her, wearing the snazziest business casual attire she’s ever seen. But there’s one problem: this woman is a ghost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Tiffany, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Daniel Riera&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brick and Mortal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rhea is excited to visit her mom and dad, who have just bought a brand-new cabin in the woods. The house seems great, except Rhea keeps seeing a figure out of the corner of her eye: a woman, standing in the woods, staring at her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Rhea, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Clay Xavier&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d435d4c0-8f20-4549-ae1d-7473098fff9e/3000x3000/eunice-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Tattoo Exorcism</title><link>podcasts/Tattoo Exorcism.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Traditional-Filipino-tattoo practitioner, &lt;a href="https://www.lanewilcken.com/#/" target="_blank"&gt;Lane Wilcken&lt;/a&gt;, is never scared when ancestral spirits visit during tattoo sessions. He knows that those spirits, the ones that are just stopping by, aren’t the ones you have to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Lane Wilcken, for sharing your story with us! Lane wrote the book on traditional Filipino tattooing — &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Filipino-Tattoos-Ancient-Modern-Wilcken/dp/0764336029" target="_blank"&gt;Filipino Tattoos: Ancient to Modern&lt;/a&gt;. Today, Lane is one of only twenty people in the world who practice Filipino tattooing in its traditional form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Lauryn Newson, produced by Zoë Ferrigno, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/df59f6f9-3fc8-4fc1-8fe2-cc8f0079f942/3000x3000/layer-17.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Lunger's Row</title><link>podcasts/Lunger's Row.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Some folks live in haunted houses. The ghosts get cozy, they move in and they don’t move out. But what if your whole neighborhood is haunted?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much, Caroline Liu, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/7d3d2c32-5b5f-47c1-9a11-6902c9bd3eac/3000x3000/lungersrow-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Steakout</title><link>podcasts/The Steakout.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Things can seem to creep and lurk in the dark — especially when you’re on duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Night Watch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Dave took on the graveyard shift at the station, he saw all kinds of stuff. But he never saw anything quite like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Dave, for sharing your story with the Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Davey Kim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steakout&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin joins the force and soon realizes that he can help everyone who crosses his path — whether they’re living or dead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the interest of protecting his identity, we’re not using this storyteller's real name. Instead, we called him “Kevin.” Thank you, Kevin, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 8 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a89bb423-985f-4d2c-a16b-c266526346b0/3000x3000/thesteakout-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Night at the Aquarium</title><link>podcasts/Night at the Aquarium.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;On Kevin’s night shift at the Monterey Bay Aquarium, things get wet, wild, and very very weird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BIG thanks to Kevin Wright and the magical Monterey Bay Aquarium. Thanks also to KAZU Radio in Monterey, California for its assistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Yari Bundy &amp; Renzo Gorrio, produced by Anne Ford, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 1 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d0f8f032-2a63-446b-91d1-93a064613cbd/3000x3000/nightattheaquarium-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Dod</title><link>podcasts/Dod.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Arin is living with his parents and siblings in Washington state when some of his long-forgotten childhood memories start coming back to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BIG thanks to, Arin and Mallory, for sharing your story with us here at Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Richard Haig, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0a67ac91-f0f8-411e-bfdc-8f0901aa78bc/3000x3000/dod-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Succubus</title><link>podcasts/The Succubus.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve heard of “Sexual Healing” but have you heard of a sexual demon? This week on Spooked, we take you to the Hollywood Hills to meet a demonic seductress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much, Colin, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Eliza Smith, original score by Doug Stewart, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c874e782-7a12-4a7e-a7e1-a35945118072/3000x3000/succubus-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Big Man</title><link>podcasts/Big Man.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When the Big Guy shows up, you keep your mouth shut. Be afraid…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you to our storyteller for sharing his experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Yari Bundy, produced by Anne Ford, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f641ad24-3060-45ef-b50c-e5634778b2b6/3000x3000/bigman-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Las Muñecas</title><link>podcasts/Las Muñecas.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Francisco finds a doll in his pocket every single day. And every single day, he gets sicker and weaker. He needs to get rid of these dolls... before they get rid of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big thanks to Francisco Vazquez for sharing your story with the Spooked. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Fernando Hernandez and Erick Yanez, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 4 Aug 2023 11:58:15 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f3420557-217e-46d6-9c25-c4c49c26cd1c/3000x3000/lasmunecas-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Three Sickles And A Roomba</title><link>podcasts/Three Sickles And A Roomba.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Diana knows that the little girl she keeps seeing in her house is a ghost. But what she doesn’t know is if this ghost means her family any harm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Diana, for sharing your story with Spooked! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/de1d1eb2-4273-4d41-9007-40c08ec7187d/3000x3000/threesicklesandaroomba-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Champ</title><link>podcasts/Champ.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Pati is really young when she loses her best friend and isn’t sure she’ll ever see him again. Until one day, he shows up, asking to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Pati, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c7e297a0-558a-45f4-817b-681204b3da98/3000x3000/champ-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Burning Look</title><link>podcasts/Burning Look.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;He’s a happy, all-American, baseball-loving kid. Then the fires start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many thanks to storyteller for sharing his experiences!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Yari Bundy, produced by Anne Ford, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Episodes drop weekly. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8fccb997-ba2b-4c92-a074-a2af8555fe54/3000x3000/burninglook-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Pinky's Place</title><link>podcasts/Pinky's Place.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Josh moves into an old hotel in Pittsburgh to help his family renovate it. As he starts to experience things he can’t explain, it quickly becomes clear to him that some people may have never left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Josh, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Daniel Riera, produced by Marisa Dodge&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8e4b0dda-d60f-4d8e-8729-48c64b1d5b7a/3000x3000/pinkyviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Wind and Fog</title><link>podcasts/Wind and Fog.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Howling wind. Swirling fog. What lurks in the mist? To whom is the wind calling?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Route 666&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Kilpatrick is coming home from the venue, celebrating a great show. He’s taking a familiar road. But tonight, the conditions are bad: hard wind, rain, and… frogs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Michael, for sharing your story. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widow’s Walk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bubba has worked at the same lighthouse in coastal Maine for years. And even though the isolation has made his coworkers crack, Bubba has always been okay. He toughs it out. Until one night, when someone emerges from the night, and knocks on the lighthouse door. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Bubba, for sharing your story with us here at Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber and Galen Koch, original score by Clay Xavier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spooked episodes drop weekly. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/22e0da18-6d42-4831-a7e0-0310cea75c11/3000x3000/windandfog-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Out of Body</title><link>podcasts/Out of Body.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Tiyi just wants to get away from the man in the closet. What happens next changes her life forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Tiyi Schippers, for sharing your story with us! You can find more of her creepy tales on &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCnaiIvWFoR9eLQ7r4yMlppA" target="_blank"&gt;YouTube.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Leon Morimoto, produced by Anne Ford, artwork by Teo Ducot &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spooked episodes drop weekly! Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/7f3c5732-4ce6-4619-a98b-70224045030c/3000x3000/outofbody-square.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Keep It Pono</title><link>podcasts/Keep It Pono.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you live in Hawaii, you know that if you see the ancient Night Marchers of the King’s Guard, you bow in reverence. And you don’t look them in the eye, under any circumstances. But Obake, Dee, and Joe Bones? They haven’t learned this lesson… yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mahalo, Obake, for sharing your story with us. If you're interested in more stories from Obake, check out his YouTube channel, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCUNN0--82T16_J6n1SWzj2Q" target="_blank"&gt;Ghosts of Hawaii&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Richard Haig, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d82faee3-2c37-465a-aece-6847c9e86aa6/3000x3000/keepitpono-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Inkwell</title><link>podcasts/The Inkwell.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Just because someone’s passed over, doesn’t mean they’re not still watching over you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Tapeworm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richie “Tapeworm” Herrera ran one of the most badass tattoo parlors in Chicago. It was haunted, and he didn’t mind that. That is, until the ghosts tried to push him out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you Anne, Chris, Tony, and Adam for telling us about the amazing &lt;a href="https://www.oldtowntatu.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Richie “Tapeworm” Herrera&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bull Ring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd loses someone he loves very much, but it seems his friend is not truly gone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Todd Narron, for sharing your stories with us. If you want more stories from Todd, check out his book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Country-Stories-Ghosts-Bad-Men/dp/1514759187" target="_blank"&gt;Country Stories of Ghosts and Bad Men&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09LMDX587/ref=redir_mob" target="_blank"&gt;Country Stories of Ghosts and Bad Men: Series 2 - The Dead Ones.&lt;/a&gt; Do not miss out on these amazing stories!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Renzo Gorrio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Episodes now drop weekly. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f72fcd15-d8cd-4bc5-9e84-56b5fa2b513d/3000x3000/inkwellviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Smell Ya Later</title><link>podcasts/Smell Ya Later.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After Laura’s husband gets a fatal diagnosis, he promises to contact her from beyond the grave. But how will she know it’s really him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Laura Packer, for sharing this special story with Spooked. Laura’s a storyteller in Minneapolis. You can learn more about Laura at her &lt;a href="https://laurapacker.com/" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Leon Morimoto, produced by Anne Ford, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episodes now drop weekly on Fridays. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f66876d3-6b35-4210-bd7e-06288f62065a/3000x3000/smellyalater-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Weeping Painting</title><link>podcasts/Weeping Painting.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Omar thinks he know his grandma. Until one day, he finds a scary portrait in her bedroom… and it’s looking at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you Omar for sharing your story with Spooked, all the way from Mexico!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leonel Garza gave Omar his voice in English. You can check out more of Leonel Garza’s acting work on his &lt;a href="https://www.leonelgarza.com/" target="_blank"&gt;website.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yáñez, original score by Nicholas Marks, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Episodes now drop weekly. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e9fc6fea-72ef-4b74-92c5-f88db21511d8/3000x3000/weepingpaintingviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Earth Angel</title><link>podcasts/Earth Angel.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Alfia is studying to be a nurse, but she soon discovers that science isn’t everything and a higher power is at work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Alfia, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Sudi Watchpress&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episodes now drop weekly on Fridays. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts!&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/af77822c-40d7-4d5d-bcc0-177067d4e97d/3000x3000/earthangelviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Northspur Storm</title><link>podcasts/Northspur Storm.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Kathy and her kids leave a busy life in Southern California to live in a little cabin in the woods, without electricity. But then, strange things start happening. It seems Kathy and her children aren’t the only occupants of the cabin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Kathy Bolte, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Episodes now drop weekly on Fridays. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/018cad38-b9f3-4cab-9fc9-ce8123c9d24e/3000x3000/northspurviii-sq-1.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Big Sleep</title><link>podcasts/The Big Sleep.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jen wakes up in a strange hospital with mysterious caretakers. Her only way out? The shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jen and Robin, for sharing your story with the Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spooked episodes now drop weekly on Fridays. Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free wherever you get your podcasts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 5 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/350decb3-eebf-476d-adb6-bb3e50dcd050/3000x3000/bigsleepviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Pee Afraid</title><link>podcasts/Pee Afraid.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Aammton Alias has a work retreat in the jungle. And when he gets there… he’s gotta go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spooked episodes now drop every week on Friday! Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free on any podcast platform. Be afraid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Dr. Aammton, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Dirk Schwarzhoff, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/54b008ad-42f8-4008-b6a6-b892de0a77d6/3000x3000/peeafraidviii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hounded</title><link>podcasts/Hounded.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Some roads are long and some roads wind. Some roads show you things you’d never think you’d find…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Story 1: Demon Dog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chuck and his family rent a cabin in the mountains every winter. One year he and his uncle are driving into town when they see something with red eyes chasing their truck: a huge, menacing wolf-like creature. When he’s older, he learns this creature has a name: The Demon Dog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the second story Chuck has graciously shared with Spooked. If you want to hear Chuck tell another spine-chilling story set in the mountains, listen to the Spooked Dismal Falls episode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber and Chris Hambrick, original score by Yari Bundy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Story 2: Deception Pass&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shirley is a trucker. She gets sent out on a job and is given a tight deadline in bad weather. During the course of her four-day trip, her life is saved twice on the exact same stretch of highway. But by who?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Shirley, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Doug Stuart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a7fa40b0-1d26-46bd-88c3-6348eb2793fd/3000x3000/hounded-viii-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Always Be Polite</title><link>podcasts/Always Be Polite.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;John Henson, a Southern Cheyenne Native American, is the go-to person when friends and family need their homes smoked off. But when he encounters a stubborn and angry cat-like entity, he has to dig deeper than ever before — all while being polite. For Spooked, and for the first time for a non-native audience, John shares his story. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episodes now drop every week on Friday! Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free on any podcast platform. Be afraid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much to John Henson for sharing your story with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Original score by Leon Morimoto, produced by Chris Hambrick + Anne Ford, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/2059f1d2-0a27-45ce-98ab-e838a113613d/3000x3000/alwaysbepolite-square.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Deer Stand</title><link>podcasts/The Deer Stand.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Dan is a hunter. His favorite place in the world is his deer stand: a platform 20 feet up in an ancient tree. One day, Dan is sitting up in the tree when he sees something that changes his life forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episodes now drop every week on Friday! Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Listen for free on any podcast platform. Be afraid…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story discuss suicide. Sensitive listeners please be advised.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Dan, for sharing your story with us here at Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen and Eliza Smith, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Sanaa Khan + Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/42bd21e4-9dd3-46fa-b250-7ba75d38e487/3000x3000/deerstand-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Dead End</title><link>podcasts/Dead End.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When we meet darkness and our road grows dim, sometimes a spirit finds us and helps guide us towards the path we’re meant to take… or avoid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spooked episodes now drop every week on Friday! Featuring brand new stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. For Luminary subscribers, previously released episodes are still on Luminary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paper Route Premonition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alyssa is taking over her friend’s paper route for the week. It’s a fun way to make a little money. There’s just one house that’s freaking her out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Alyssa for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Yari Bundy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stormwalker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Roberta, there’s nothing scarier than the thought of being caught out in a big storm. One day, her worst fear comes true… and then someone shows up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Roberta, for sharing your story with Spooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Yari Bundy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0b36e646-d51b-409d-8e45-dd754cc2d0af/3000x3000/stormwalker-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Season VIII Trailer</title><link>podcasts/Season VIII Trailer.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Starting Friday, April 7th Spooked drops…WEEKLY! We have held back the darkness long enough and at long last… Spooked will be available for free on ALL podcast platforms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episodes will drop every week on Friday! Featuring brand NEW stories -- along with episodes previously available only by subscription. Be afraid. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Luminary subscribers, previously released episodes are still on Luminary.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 5 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/79bf00a1-f29c-452b-ae65-737e4850d49a/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>D-E-B-R-A</title><link>podcasts/D-E-B-R-A.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;After the birth of her second child, Elijah, Sabrina starts to wonder if she’s brought home more from the hospital than just her new baby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Sabrina, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Yari Bundy, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/1b8019eb-522b-4ae0-b66f-b2d68fb0df4f/3000x3000/debra-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Sinkhole</title><link>podcasts/The Sinkhole.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;One day, while out landscaping his yard, Moses reaches into the dirt and pulls out a handful of bones. He wants to find out who they belong to. But that might not be such a good idea…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Moses Thompson, for sharing your story with the Spooked! Folks, if you want to know more about Moses and his house, check out &lt;a href="https://tucson.com/news/local/current-residents-previous-tenants-share-hallowed-ground-in-historic-neighborhood/article_ca6877d9-812d-5b8d-b5ce-7b4d0514a041.html" target="_blank"&gt;this article. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Yari Bundy, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:31:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/279fb07c-9468-485b-8aee-87a1ad37e056/3000x3000/the-sinkhole-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Pali Lookout</title><link>podcasts/Pali Lookout.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s March 1980, and best friends Lopaka and Sean decide to ditch class and head to the Pali Lookout, a tourist destination just outside of Honolulu on the island of Oahu. They’re hanging out, taking in the sights… but nothing can prepare them for what happens when they decide to venture off the beaten path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Lopaka Kapanui, for lifting back the veil with Spooked! If you want more stories about spirits, legends, and the &lt;a href="https://www.mysteries-of-hawaii.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Mysteries of Hawaii&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Lopaka’s got you covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 04:31:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/40777c3a-4e72-4ef0-bfa2-c1d1a41fc360/3000x3000/moowahine-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hotel Hell-o Dolly</title><link>podcasts/Hotel Hell-o Dolly.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Hotels and dolls can be full of charm — others are horrifying and cause alarm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hotel Hell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kimberly was expecting a luxurious hotel room. Someone in it… was expecting her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Kimberly and Colin for sharing your story!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Doug Stuart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dolly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some dolls are pretty, some dolls are nice, some dolls are waiting for you... in the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BIG thanks, Mary, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Ella June Pierson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 7 Oct 2022 04:31:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d345cff6-ebab-44e8-a428-3598a5aa9ea8/3000x3000/dolly-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Matt's Flat</title><link>podcasts/Matt's Flat.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Matt is calm, peaceful, and very chill, but his apartment has a dark past. On one rainy night in Birmingham, his flat mate finally makes herself known, and her story unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a86c15da-783e-4ee5-891a-1fdabef050ce/3000x3000/mattsflat-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Los Chaneques</title><link>podcasts/Los Chaneques.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Saulo knows the stories about the mischievous creatures who lurk in the forests and beaches of Oaxaca. But one night a hunt for turtle eggs becomes a search for the truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Saulo, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Erick Yañez, original score by Leon Morimoto, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Erick doesn’t just work for Spooked, he is also the producer of a horror fiction podcast that you are gonna love. Check out &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://psicofonias.com.mx/" target="_blank"&gt;Psicofonías&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; wherever you get your podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 9 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c300f26a-364d-4e83-b588-3e753d3ae006/3000x3000/loschaneques-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Dad and the Three Caskets</title><link>podcasts/Dad and the Three Caskets.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Spooked's own Annie Nguyen shares her family’s ghost story. When her father got the call from his siblings and cousins back in Vietnam, asking him to help them find their ancestors’ missing caskets, he got on the first plane out of California. But when he got there, he realized they needed to call on higher powers to help them locate the long-lost grave sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BIG love and thanks to Poppa Nguyen, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Renzo Gorrio, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Translation by George Q. Nguyen - please note the translation was condensed for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 07:03:50 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/94d5ab26-60f4-4cd8-9b6a-52268d44f9da/3000x3000/spooked-624-dadandthreecaskets-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Dismal Falls</title><link>podcasts/Dismal Falls.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;There are some places, deep in the woods, far away from civilization, that are magical. Chuck is hiking deep in the Appalachian woods when he stumbles upon one of these places: Dismal Falls. But Dismal Falls isn’t all fairies and rainbows. It’s a place of dark magic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Chuck, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Greta Weber, original score by Clay Xavier, artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 07:18:41 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e02dbaf6-49db-4c86-ae6f-0588ad50c910/3000x3000/spooked-621-dismalfalls-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Romeo &amp; Juliet</title><link>podcasts/Romeo &amp; Juliet.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;A pair of star-crossed lovers encounter the paranormal in fair Wisconsin, where we lay our scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Kelsey Brennan &amp; Andy Truschinski, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zöe Ferrigno, original score by Nicholas Marks&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/5daaadbe-c31f-4593-9bad-4230bc4799b8/3000x3000/spooked-609-romeojuliet2.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Corporal Cummings</title><link>podcasts/Corporal Cummings.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s 1967. Jerry has been drafted and just landed in Vietnam. He keeps meeting another young soldier, Cummings… and every time they run into each other, something terrible seems to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode does contain scenes of war and combat violence, sensitive listeners please be advised.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Jerry, for sharing your story with us! Learn more about &lt;a href="https://jerryglazer.medium.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Jerry&lt;/a&gt; on his &lt;a href="https://www.vietnamjerry.com/" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/VietnamJerry67" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Daniel Riera&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 2 Oct 2021 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/2e3a60e1-4f89-4647-a23b-0905130c7bab/3000x3000/spooked-605-corpcummings-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Cliffhanger</title><link>podcasts/Cliffhanger.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Bill is home from college, on his way to meet his girlfriend, when his car swerves off the road…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Bill Love, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/3762528b-353b-4246-999b-4c20204146dc/3000x3000/cliffhanger.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Flora and the Fox</title><link>podcasts/Flora and the Fox.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Flora heads to China to spend time with family for the summer, she realizes her young cousin is acting weird. Almost like he’s someone… or some&lt;em&gt;thing&lt;/em&gt; else entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Flora, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Annie Nguyen, original score by Doug Stuart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 04:10:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/fe155923-9ff7-43c4-a5be-56c42b0bb697/3000x3000/spooked-603-floraandfox-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Green Demon</title><link>podcasts/Green Demon.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Austin’s dad starts having night terrors, the family thinks it’s just nightmares -- but Austin thinks something else is going on. He soon discovers that there is an actual demon plaguing his father… and Austin must confront it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Austin, for sharing your story with Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f784ab54-6b06-472f-a782-f6778f9de425/3000x3000/spooked-602-greendemon-sq.jpg?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Fright at the Museum</title><link>podcasts/Fright at the Museum.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jen is about to start an internship at a museum. But this isn’t a typical museum… It's built inside two old, historic mansions. By this time, the original owners of these two old homes are long gone -- or are they?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Jen, for sharing your story with the Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Leon Morimoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 4 Sep 2021 04:29:27 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/6b94d8d4-b67f-47f9-9bec-451368014d0a/3000x3000/spooked-601-frightatthemuseum-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>A Murder of Crows</title><link>podcasts/A Murder of Crows.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Birds talk to each other about everything -- where to find food, where to roost, when to migrate. What messages might they have for us?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Head&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all know the old wives’ tales: don’t walk under a ladder or you’ll have bad luck; don’t step on the crack or you’ll break your mama’s back. Dan is about to discover another, more sinister omen… with deadly consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Dan, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Anne Ford, original score by Maryam Qudus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Murder of Crows&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mike is pretty sure he’s going crazy. Every time he sees a crow, it seems like it’s trying to tell him something: to watch out, to beware. What are they trying to warn him of?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks, Mike, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Alyia Yates, original score by Lauryn Newson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a78732b2-febc-47a9-95c4-e8e673af47d3/3000x3000/murderofcrows-sq-vi.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Friends on the Other Side</title><link>podcasts/Friends on the Other Side.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, spirits reach out and ask us for help. And sometimes, they reach out to give us what we need, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;STORIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Night Nurse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dennis is a nurse, a helper. But when spirits of former patients reach out to him, he’s not sure if he can care for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big love to Dennis for sharing his story with the Spooked!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Chris Hambrick, original score by Dakim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All Dogs go to Heaven&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s confirmed: all dogs do go to heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Kristin Kent, for sharing your story with us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by Zoë Ferrigno, original score by Moises Nunez&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artwork by Teo Ducot&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:26:04 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/05b28f8b-623e-4279-84ea-a4188ff8c53e/3000x3000/friendsvi-sq.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Don't Wanna Fright No More</title><link>podcasts/Don't Wanna Fright No More.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When singer/songwriter &amp; former frontwoman of the Alabama Shakes, Brittany Howard, comes up against a hostile spirit in her home, she has to decide: who’s going to get to stay? Brittany... or the ghost?&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c813d638-b9d1-47e3-9990-1659f0173bd1/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Skinwalker</title><link>podcasts/Skinwalker.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Lee’s great grandfather, his grandfather, and his father have all seen him: the shapeshifter. They know this man has the power to curse them, to hurt them. Lee wonders: is this man coming for him too? &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 5 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c8120b90-b74d-4910-b592-7ae4b3c63a96/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Haunting of Radio Centro</title><link>podcasts/The Haunting of Radio Centro.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone who works at Radio Centro knows it’s haunted. But Guillermo, the host on the station’s paranormal show “Tell it Tonight” is about to discover that he has psychic powers that make him susceptible to the station’s haunts. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 2 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a4d39514-7aa9-43f2-b71a-82cdea4fa0e1/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Petrony</title><link>podcasts/Petrony.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;David’s family has owned the same plot of farmland in North Carolina for over 300 years. As he gets older, he starts to realize that some family members have never really left.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/da5450ca-56bc-4f12-9eca-14c6d836bd88/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Teacher’s Pet</title><link>podcasts/Teacher’s Pet.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Kristen Cortez is a new teacher in beautiful Los Gatos, California. From her classroom window, she can see rolling, golden hills. Redwood trees. The sun is almost always shining. And yet… something lurks. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d41eb475-6a53-42cd-895a-63db43a2d3f2/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Take Me Home</title><link>podcasts/Take Me Home.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You are on your smoke break at Walmart. You look down and see a box: inside is a ceramic lamb with a note around its neck asking you to take it home. Do you: a) burn it; b) throw it in the trash, or c) take it home?&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f3a25152-fbae-43cc-a5dd-b6c32e8f70b5/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Campfire Tales VII</title><link>podcasts/Campfire Tales VII.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Get warmed up for Season V! &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/6285cca2-fdb8-4ea8-8b13-d245fce323d8/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Fog</title><link>podcasts/The Fog.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Blair can’t see his hands in front of his face. He can’t see the ground beneath his feet. He’s not in the dark: he’s in a thick cloud of fog. And then, a voice emerges from the mist. This story comes to us from Australia, the original Upside Down.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 3 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/002ad3ae-e51a-417e-a009-d78b5711b105/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Isabelle</title><link>podcasts/Isabelle.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Betsy keeps seeing a young girl at night in her room. She stands at the end of Betsy’s bed and stares at her. She comes back, over and over: night after night; year after year. Betsy knows she wants something, but she has to figure out &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f082103b-9682-42c6-9455-475f44b9d177/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Trespassers</title><link>podcasts/The Trespassers.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the supernatural: don’t poke the bear. Don’t kick the hive. Don’t mess around. Because, when it comes to the supernatural: you’re gonna get what’s coming for you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/6d7053bf-f56c-461e-b876-e63cf735f0d0/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Lopaka</title><link>podcasts/Lopaka.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Lopaka and his adopted father don’t get along. That is, until forces from beyond the veil intervene.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/96be6fe5-2639-49ea-901e-51ab4b5bfd6f/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Iconic</title><link>podcasts/Iconic.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;You &lt;em&gt;know &lt;/em&gt;the most haunted places. The houses, the castles, the hotels. And you &lt;em&gt;know &lt;/em&gt;the most haunted objects. The mirrors, the necklaces, the dolls. In this episode, we take you to the Stanley Hotel and introduce you to Robert the Doll.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e5da881f-32cb-490b-9731-0b27a45d0769/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Santi</title><link>podcasts/Santi.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When Maribel loses her little brother Santi, her very best friend in the world, she learns that love is sometimes stronger than death. We travel to Mexico for this very special Spooked tale. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/43a99320-dfbc-47a1-9b76-a1e420cf77c3/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Portal - Snap Bonus</title><link>podcasts/Portal - Snap Bonus.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Percy was just a young graduate student researching PTSD, but the closer she got to understanding the inner workings of one soldier’s trauma, the more she lost her own footing in reality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/3eb37014-a436-4eaa-b7ce-bd99b9da48b3/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Sharp Tooth Boy</title><link>podcasts/Sharp Tooth Boy.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Bonnie Blagg and her two friends call for Bloody Mary in the mirror on her dresser during a middle school sleepover. Bonnie thinks nothing of it until a ghost boy with long, sharp, bloody teeth appears in her bedroom every single night after that. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Friday the 13th!&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/2cb0ab89-af59-42e5-972e-b0144be8258f/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Tales from the Smokehouse</title><link>podcasts/Tales from the Smokehouse.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Cursed cat bones. Dead dogs. A haunted pond. Master storyteller Todd Narron is our tour guide as we explore the mysterious, spooky American South.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Todd Narron, for sharing your stories with us! If you want more stories from Todd, check out his incredible books:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Country-Stories-Ghosts-Bad-Men/dp/1514759187" target="_blank"&gt;Country Stories of Ghosts and Bad Men&lt;/a&gt; &amp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09LMDX587/ref=redir_mob" target="_blank"&gt;Country Stories of Ghosts and Bad Men: Series 2 - The Dead Ones.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not miss out on these amazing stories!&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 2 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/54612fe9-5b5a-419a-bee8-5b4b3fe0d032/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Mrs. Hagstrom</title><link>podcasts/Mrs. Hagstrom.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;When supernatural forces come for her kids, Curtis’s mom stands strong. Mrs. Hagstrom may be the meanest Spooked ghost yet...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Season III is ALIVE!! There are 26 new episodes of &lt;a href="https://luminary.link/OF8c2ygBkZ" target="_blank"&gt;Spooked&lt;/a&gt; coming this season each week through Halloween and into a spooky November. To listen to them all, download the Luminary mobile app or go to &lt;a href="https://luminarypodcasts.com/" target="_blank"&gt;LuminaryPodcasts.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0290ba88-3e88-45fc-906b-43dcc2aada4d/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Thin Place</title><link>podcasts/The Thin Place.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Martin is a paramedic. He has a gift for saving peoples' lives. He also has another, darker, gift--one that he doesn’t want to use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8aca94b8-b9fa-4551-a3d8-3360b11df7a4/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Night Whistler</title><link>podcasts/The Night Whistler.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Night Whistler:&lt;/strong&gt; Cheryl decided that she could make the best out of living in a haunted house. Nothing bad could happen if she made friends with the ghost… right?&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/555680ac-ce8b-406f-889a-588fe85f5482/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Intruders</title><link>podcasts/The Intruders.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;La Posada:&lt;/strong&gt; What if your great-great-grandmother comes back from the dead, but doesn’t visit you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re Gonna Get Scratched:&lt;/strong&gt; Three kids go inside an abandoned house… turns out, it’s not empty.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/faa69e43-776d-492d-88a9-2f65677f1cba/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Under The Stairs</title><link>podcasts/Under The Stairs.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Basement: When one of Daniel’s kids started seeing ghosts, he was scared. When two of his kids started seeing ghosts, he was petrified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the Stairs: Mido discovers that the former tenants of her apartment left some breadcrumbs behind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/c1bc2187-a4dd-4e83-88f5-2e5be3b364bb/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Skagway</title><link>podcasts/Skagway.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frances:&lt;/strong&gt; Cori suspects she’s got a second roommate who she can’t see, and who may very well be contacting her from beyond the veil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lydia:&lt;/strong&gt; The wait staff at the Red Onion Saloon in Skagway, Alaska uncover the tragic story of their notorious ghost, Lydia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/958ad322-78ae-4d83-99c7-186163e998ae/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Holy Ghost</title><link>podcasts/Holy Ghost.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Possession: When Sara appears to be cursed, her grandmother calls on a coven of witches for the cure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Healing: When it comes to miracles, lightning doesn’t strike twice. But Paul doesn’t know that yet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/7889a960-a14c-470b-af83-8384fc07d96f/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Ghost Town</title><link>podcasts/Ghost Town.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Mine: California is gold country. Miner Shannon Poe discovers that not every abandoned gold mine has been vacated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mission: An empty old church. An open door. A sight no one will believe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 4 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/d6006c6e-7fdc-4894-898f-2ebb4aefb24e/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Hush</title><link>podcasts/Hush.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Libby:&lt;/strong&gt; Jennifer and her daughter Taylor both know their family home is haunted… but they don’t want to share that secret, even with each other&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Voy a Tener Nietos:&lt;/strong&gt; Maria’s mother always wanted a son. And when Maria had a son, of her own, her mother didn’t get enough time with him. So when she died, she made sure to came back to be with her beloved nieto.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/8750aea4-835b-4675-bf11-c980a0abe4b0/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Something In The Walls</title><link>podcasts/Something In The Walls.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Visage:&lt;/strong&gt; A man is hired to do remodel work on a notorious haunted house. But something inside the house doesn’t want anything to change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decorations:&lt;/strong&gt;  Paintings start appearing on the walls. Dark, odd, and disturbed. All Nic knows is, something sinister is at work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/3b06345a-01f7-4648-bf31-844b9ecc4981/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Smells Like Teen Spirits</title><link>podcasts/Smells Like Teen Spirits.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Mammoth Mountain Poltergeist:&lt;/strong&gt; Tom Ross finds evil lurking in the most unlikely place: a California ski chalet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Moonshiner’s Daughter:&lt;/strong&gt; Alex doesn’t know the man who lurks on her property, who sometimes appears in her home… but he seems to know her.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/69ab7f5b-e7f3-4ea9-b37f-7e741f0ece02/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Perfect Tenant</title><link>podcasts/The Perfect Tenant.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Perfect Tenant:&lt;/strong&gt; Steven LaChance found the perfect home… or, did the home find him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ghosty:&lt;/strong&gt; When your kid tells you she’s just seen a ghost, you might want to believe her.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/2963cc31-5794-45e5-b030-ba1852590853/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>37 Seconds</title><link>podcasts/37 Seconds.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;37 Seconds:&lt;/strong&gt; Stephanie Arnold was pregnant with her second child, and she couldn’t have been more excited. Until she got her first premonition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to check out &lt;a href="https://www.googleadservices.com/pagead/aclk?sa=L&amp;ai=DChcSEwjg8_bMia7bAhWQ12QKHYGDD48YABABGgJwag&amp;ohost=www.google.com&amp;cid=CAESQOD2Za-9c53_DMwqAqMNDp2yD0UJdUnD--a0gv11gS0nzRZNsW8Dq_36ByElpe2tQ_s-VLZF7XcicXOEOqjWeDU&amp;sig=AOD64_00VxcVEqwozCLdH54JG2--6NnjbQ&amp;ctype=5&amp;q=&amp;ved=0ahUKEwiF1e_Mia7bAhUN658KHd2FDeIQww8ILQ&amp;adurl=" target="_blank"&gt;Stephanie’s book "37 Seconds&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/91c57979-421f-4f15-89b7-fad934ba2ba5/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Creepy Crawly</title><link>podcasts/Creepy Crawly.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Birds:&lt;/strong&gt; As a little boy in Richmond Virginia, raising pigeons, Ray Christian made a friend with the same hobby. But there was something mysterious about Ray’s new pal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Taxidermist:&lt;/strong&gt; When Tracey started doing taxidermy, she assumed all her subjects would be dead. Until she met a squirrel who didn't seem quite right.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/b1230fdb-cc3e-45c8-a7d1-21c4832a42a3/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Iron Gate</title><link>podcasts/The Iron Gate.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iron Gate:&lt;/strong&gt; An American soldier takes over an empty house in Baghdad and encounters the one threat he is powerless against.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/48a09ea3-4d47-44c3-b70e-d38b738f2d6d/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Restless</title><link>podcasts/Restless.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Curse of Mr. Smith:&lt;/strong&gt;  Every time Randi’s grandma looked out her kitchen window, she’d see him, standing on the lawn: Mr. Smith. Who was Mr. Smith? What did he want? And why was he so sad?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Angel of Death:&lt;/strong&gt; When Ron was working at Overbrook, one of New Jersey’s oldest and most notorious asylums, he knew the place was… off. Little did he know that he would see something there that would change his life forever.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 9 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f8481ddb-3310-420f-9c72-02dea58f5082/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Wraith</title><link>podcasts/The Wraith.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Teresa can see dead people. And she’s not afraid… until she meets HER.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 7 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f2e2ae6f-bf18-4235-9930-55fc81156530/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Final Act</title><link>podcasts/Final Act.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories: "Cowboy Whiteout" - A woman gets an unlikely savior when she’s lost in a snowstorm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Flesh-Eating Bacteria" - A mortician-in-training has his worst shift yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Big Al" - A caregiver gets a visit from one of his late patients.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f8e8f0d0-1b15-4f7a-b238-fbca286e009f/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Lost</title><link>podcasts/Lost.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories: "Cat Scratch Fever" - Something is here, scratching, clawing its way out of the darkness... &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Invisible Children" - What do you do when you find three ghost children living in your attic? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Pastor’s Oil"  - Jenny is up in her room, she’s shaking like there’s something inside of her. And Glynn is about to find out what . . .&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/80c1a43f-d9d1-4b26-990a-752794677b5f/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Clown Zombie</title><link>podcasts/Clown Zombie.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories: "Clown Zombie" - What happens when you make a happy clown very, very angry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Polaroid Phantom" &lt;strong&gt;- &lt;/strong&gt;Two men discover that the ghosts in their home are not camera shy. Pics at &lt;a href="http://www.seeingthingsthebook.com"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.seeingthingsthebook.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/67c5af10-c769-441e-9dee-5700260316c7/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Summoning</title><link>podcasts/The Summoning.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories:  &lt;strong&gt;"Spirit on the Board"&lt;/strong&gt; - What happens when a group of kids conjure a spirit?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"The Seance"&lt;/strong&gt; - A long-lost love comes to town for a visit, and he's been dead for years. Produced by Bob Carlson and KCRW's Unfictional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Dollhouse"&lt;/strong&gt; - Ali Standish came home after surgery and was shocked to find her grandmother in the living room with a gift--a dollhouse.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e5c0ce2a-ab82-453c-b9e0-fac98b8746d1/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Unholy Water</title><link>podcasts/Unholy Water.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories: " &lt;strong&gt;Devil’s Water" -&lt;/strong&gt; What happens when your god-fearing family agrees to dance with the dark side in a moment of desperation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Hot Water" -&lt;/strong&gt; Three girls planned a relaxing trip to a remote hot springs, and ended up fighting for their lives against a shadowy figure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/29e415e4-cacd-460c-9233-e9e32ac4c209/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Black Rose</title><link>podcasts/The Black Rose.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories:  &lt;strong&gt;"Great Aunt Rose" -  &lt;/strong&gt; When Christina McKenna’s cruel aunt comes back from the grave to make amends--she’s not sure if she can forgive. Read more about Christina in her book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Mother-Wore-Yellow-Dress-childhood/dp/1499735308" target="_blank"&gt;My Mother Wore A Yellow Dress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"The Unicorn Prince" -&lt;/strong&gt; Every year, Maria's aunt bought her a cute doll for her doll collection, but then came this one. This story comes to us from our Spooked listener Maria Serratore-Gunter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Mon, 9 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/ca7c7a3a-badf-41c2-8799-bf5d53a58f6e/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>A Friend In The Forest</title><link>podcasts/A Friend In The Forest.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories: "A Boy Named Thomas" - Shane Dunphy spent years working with kids as a social worker. He’d seen it all until he met a little boy named Gregory. For more, get Shane Dunphy’s book &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Boy-They-Tried-Hide-forgotten-ebook/dp/B019NFEJYA" target="_blank"&gt;The Boy They Tried to Hide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 5 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e52cdd0a-cc96-42a6-9a10-4c50c8f43554/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Shadow Men</title><link>podcasts/The Shadow Men.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Witch Cage:&lt;/strong&gt; A woman buys a medieval jail… and tries to make it her home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phantom Border Agent:&lt;/strong&gt; A border agent encounters his long-dead colleague in the middle of the desert.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Sun, 1 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/f5db3e5d-8809-4a65-8998-7948d804f890/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Possession</title><link>podcasts/Possession.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Indonesian Ghost Show" - When a TV crew shows up to film a ghost show their disrespect angers the gods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Daikon" - Susan's dog Daikon kept giving signs that an intruder was haunting her old Victorian in New Orleans. Then one night in October, the intruder crossed the line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e8c26f31-04fb-4775-bc0b-0eb5d2acff1d/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Curse</title><link>podcasts/The Curse.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stories&lt;/strong&gt; : "La Bruja" Your family is cursed--who you gonna call? La Bruja.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nestor Gomez is a storyteller based in Chicago. You can find him on Twitter @&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/soloyochapin" target="_blank"&gt;soloyochapin&lt;/a&gt; and at &lt;a href="http://www.nestorgomezstoryteller.com/" target="_blank"&gt;his website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/e2a79164-7882-4484-903a-0a29a6fc4bef/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Borderlands</title><link>podcasts/Borderlands.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Border Boogeyman" - &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Out-Foot-Nightly-Patrols-Ghostly/dp/0692488383" target="_blank"&gt;Rocky Elmore&lt;/a&gt; worked as a border patrol agent and out there, in the pitch black, he was never sure if he was completely alone.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The Seer" - The trouble began in Sri Lanka, when Chandra’s aunt woke up one day and couldn’t move her arms or legs.  The doctors had no answers, but a mysterious priest did. &lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0cae4ec3-a560-489b-bee1-3affd2ee9dfe/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>Lost In Time</title><link>podcasts/Lost In Time.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stories: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Time Warp Saloon"&lt;/strong&gt; -  The neon sign blinks at the roadhouse bar. The jukebox plays an old tune as the bartender shouts,  "Last Call." Just one more. Why not? What could it hurt?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story came to &lt;a href="http://www.wnycstudios.org/spookedpodcast.org" target="_blank"&gt;Spooked&lt;/a&gt; from Jim Harold’s Campfire Podcast, hosted by Jim Harold, check it out at &lt;a href="http://www.wnycstudios.org/JimHarold.com" target="_blank"&gt;JimHarold.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Love Letters"&lt;/strong&gt; - Mark Spencer lived in the haunted house with the ghost of Ladell--and we are eternally grateful that he stuck around long enough to bring us his story.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Fri, 8 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/a0df42f2-b23b-4589-8757-d469d3980812/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item><item><title>The Watcher</title><link>podcasts/The Watcher.mp3</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories:  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Houdini’s Promise" - Can a pact between two brothers survive death?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The Night Mother" - It’s the middle of the night. You’re not even 15, and you’re home alone with your little brother. You’re waiting for your mom to come home.  What would happen if she didn’t make it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Voice In The Woods" - When the voice says "Stop" you stay perfectly still.  And when the voice says "Run!" you had better run.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Thu, 7 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><image>https://image.simplecastcdn.com/images/2c8526/2c852645-1ded-4c1b-afd8-faabbc311c4f/0449b539-d344-4cb4-ba29-e0cc310608ea/3000x3000/spooked-8-logo-prx-kqed.png?aid=rss_feed</image></item></channel></rss>